(Penny:)...it got very real very fast
and I panicked.
(Leonard:)Why? What are you afraid of?
(Penny:)Well, what if we do go out and I do
something stupid and dump you again?
(Leonard:)What if I dump you?
(Penny:)Come on, be serious.
(Leonard:)Well, how about if we don't think
about this as a relationship?
(Leonard:)It could be more like
a new version of software.
(Leonard:)Penny and Leonard 2.0.
(Leonard:)We can test it internally,
shake out the bugs...
(Leonard:)...and if we both feel it's solid,
then we'll roll it out to the public.
(Penny:)We don't tell people
we're back together?
(Leonard:)Exactly.
We pretend like our date went badly.
(Penny:)Well, we don't really have to pretend.
(Leonard:)And we let them think that we decided
to just be friends...
(Leonard:)...and that everything's cool.
(Penny:)Okay. Great.
(Penny:)Hey, I just remembered.
I still got one of your inhalers.